Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 447, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Railway Labor Organizations National Group Insurance Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 447, Folder 8)
    Notes: Provided under Group Policy Contract GA-23000 as amended effective March 1, 1968, issued by the Travelers Insurance Company. 2 copies
  - Item 3: The Health and welfare plan of the nation's railroads and the railway labor organizations, 1977; Publication (Box 447, Folder 8)
    Notes: As decribed in group policy contact GA-23000 as amended effective January 1, 1977. Issued by the Travelers Insurance Company
  - Item 4: AFL-CIO looks at foreign trade: --a policy for the sixties, 1961; Publication (Box 447, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Predetermined motion time systems in the U.S.A., Publication (Box 447, Folder 8)
    Notes: A critical appraisal of synthetic work standards systems from both technical and collective bargaining standpoints
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: State and local taxes; Federal taxes: a handbook on problems & solutions, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: AFL-CIO looks at foreign trade: --a policy for the sixties, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Economic programs & policies for the 60's, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: article - The impact of automation-a challenge to America, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Automation-the three-legged stool, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
    Notes: Reprint of a three-part article published in The American Pressman
  - Item 6: An analysis of the Kennedy Trade Program, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
    Author: AFL- CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Dept. of Research
  - Item 7: Electronic computers and the human brain, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Trade adjustment program, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Automation requires changes in economic and employment patterns, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Employment changes and union growth, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Creating jobs through shorter hours, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Nov. 1962, AFL-CIO American Federationist. 2 copies
  - Item 2: The unequal sharing of U.S. Wealth, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Reducing hours: choices and costs, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Oct. 1962, AFL-CIO American Federationist. 2 copies
  - Item 4: The long trend to shorter hours, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Aug. 1962, AFL-CIO American Federationist. 2 copies
  - Item 5: Longer vacations through bargaining, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Dec. 1962, AFL-CIO American Federationist. 2 copies
  - Item 6: U.S. unemployment compared to other nations, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The balance of payments-a 'crisis' in perspective, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from May 1962, AFL-CIO Federationist
  - Item 8: Implications of automation, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The recent record of U.S. Foreign Trade Exports and Imports (overall and major categories), 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Modern monopolies and the public interest, 1961; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: America's unmet public service needs, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Sept. 1962, AFL-CIO American Federationist. 2 copies
  - Item 12: The common market and the United States, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Feb. 1962, AFL-CIO American Federationist.
  - Item 13: The Specter of rising unemployment, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Electronic data processing., 1958; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
    Notes: Article. Second copy
  - Item 15: Implications of automation, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Moonlighting - its cause and effect, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Labor's viewpoint in applications of computers.., 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 448, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Profit-sharing in the United States, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 3)
    Author: Seymour Brandwein
    Notes: Article. Reprint of article from May 1962 issue of Free Labour World.
  - Item 2: The common market, 1962; Publication (Box 448, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: AFL-CIO Economic and Legislative Conference -- article -- Consumer Protection; International Trade (Jan. 22-25, 1962), Publication (Box 448, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Shorter hours: to create jobs, 1964; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Automation the three-legged stool, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Strikes: myth vs. reality, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Mar. 1963, AFL-CIO American Federationist. 2 copies
  - Item 4: The energy revolution: peril and promise, 1964; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Dec. 1964, AFL-CIO Federationist
  - Item 5: The shorter workweek trend, 1964; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Dec. 1964, AFL-CIO Federationist.
  - Item 6: The Blue-Sky sweatshop, 1964; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from June 1964, AFL-CIO Federationist.
  - Item 7: Shorter hours to create jobs, 1964; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from April 1964, AFL-CIO Federationist.
  - Item 8: The truth about 'lie' detectors, 1964; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: TVA: the controversial success, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Apr. 1963, AFL-CIO Federationist. 2 copies
  - Item 10: The new trade act: too to expand markets, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Jan. 1963, AFL-CIO Federationist. 2 copies
  - Item 11: Wage gains under bargaining, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Sept. 1963, AFL-CIO Federationist.
  - Item 12: New directions in bargaining, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Nov. 1963, AFL-CIO American Federationist.
  - Item 13: The positive role of fiscal policy, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Jan. 1963, AFL-CIO American Federationist. 2 copies
  - Item 14: America's need: social services and jobs, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. Reprinted from Aug. 1963, AFL-CIO Federationist.
  - Item 15: The coming crisis: youth without work, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Employer's duty to furnish union with data on production standards, wage incentives and job evaluation, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 448, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Predetermined motion time systems in the U.S.A., Publication (Box 448, Folder 5)
    Notes: A critical appraisal of synthetic work standards systems from both technical and collective bargaining standpoints. Second copy
  - Item 2: Labor looks at education, 1963; Publication (Box 448, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Statement by the General Board of the AFL-CIO on the 1968 party platforms and the candidates for the President and Vice President of the United States, Publication (Box 448, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: article - The City worker's budget $9,200 a year, 1966; Publication (Box 448, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Correspondence: Enclosed are copies of two statements on current economic issues, adopted by the AFL-CIO Executive Council on Aug. 24, and a background paper on these issues, 1966; Publication (Box 448, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Migrant farm workers and foreign contract labor - Resolution no. 132 - Submitted by Committee on Resolutions, 1951; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Fair Labor Standards Act: Resolution no. 198 (Resoultions Book 3, P. 85), 1965; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Sixth Constitutional Convention, AFL-CIO, Resolution No. 167 -- Civil Rights, 1965; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: AFL-CIO Resolutions - No. 59 to No. 112, 1957; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: AFL-CIO Resolutions - no. 84 to 182; book 2, 1963; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: AFL-CIO Resolutions - no. 167 to 199; book 2, 1967; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Report No. 1 - AFL-CIO, Resolutions Committee, Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Report No. 2 - AFL-CIO, Resolutions Committee, Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: AFL-CIO resolutions on economic issues, 1955; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
    Notes: Adopted by the First Constitutional Convention of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, December, 1955.
  - Item 10: AFL-CIO resolutions on collective bargaining and related issues, 1955; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
    Notes: Adopted by first constitutional convention of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, December 1955.
  - Item 11: AFL-CIO 1955 Convention resolution on civil liberties and internal security, Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: AFL-CIO 1955 Convention resolution on health and welfare plan administration, Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Policy resolutions on education, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
    Notes: Adopted September 1959 by the third Constitutional Convention.
  - Item 14: Policy resolutions on economic issues, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Policy resolutions, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
    Notes: Adopted September 1959 by the third constitutional convention.
  - Item 16: Resolutions Committee report no. 2, 1957; Publication (Box 449, Folder 1)
    Notes: Report to the Second Constitutional Convention, American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: b resolutions reported from no. 72.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Text of the AFL-CIO internal disputes plan, Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: AFL-CIO 1955 Convention resolution on civil liberties and internal security, Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Resolution on the achievement of labor unity, 1955; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: AFL-CIO 1955 Convention resolution on atomic energy and power, 1956; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: AFL-CIO, 1955 Convention resolution on civil rights, 1956; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: AFL-CIO 1955 Convention resolution on education, 1956; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: AFL-CIO resolutions on social security welfare and related issues, 1956; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
    Notes: Adopted by First Constitutional Convention of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, December 1955
  - Item 8: AFL-CIO 1955 convention resolutions on foreign policy, 1956; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
    Notes: Adopted at the first constitutional convention of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations at New York City, December 5-8, 1955
  - Item 9: Policy resolutions of the AFL-CIO, 1956; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
    Notes: Adopted by the first constitutional convention of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, December 1955. 2 copies
  - Item 10: AFL-CIO 1955 Convention resolution on children and youth, 1956; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: AFL-CIO 1955 Convention resolution on Housing and Community Service, 1956; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Policy resolutions on Social Security & Related Issues, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
    Notes: Adopted September 1959 by the third constitutional convention of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations.
  - Item 13: Policy resolutions on Housing, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
    Notes: Adopted September, 1959 by the third constitutional convention of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations.
  - Item 14: Resolutions Committee report no. 1, 1957; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
    Notes: Report to the Second Constitutional Convention, American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: resolutions reported from no. 71.
  - Item 15: Resolutions Committee report no. 3, 1957; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
    Notes: Report to the Second Constitutional Convention, American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations: resolutions reported from no. 142 (Including No. 130)
  - Item 16: Resolution no. 62 - Amendment of the Election Law, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Second AFL-CIO National Conference on Safety and Occupational Health, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Subject was safety, Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
    Author: Richard F. Walsh
  - Item 3: Safety by contract: a report on safety clauses in collective bargaining agreements, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
    Author: George T. Brown
  - Item 4: Job hazards kill one American worker every five minutes, Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Killing OSHA means killing workers. Stop Reagan! Save OSHA!, Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: AFL-CIO Safety Program, Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: How to apply, AFL-CIO College merit scholarships, Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: We're promoting safety in your local, Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The Occupational Safety and Health Act: what it covers, how it works, how to use it., 1971; Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Cooperation for safety, 1956; Publication (Box 449, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 449, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Interface, 1970; Publication (Box 449, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1970)
  - Item 2: Interface, 1971; Publication (Box 449, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.2:no.1-3 (1971)
  - Item 3: Interface, 1973; Publication (Box 449, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1-3 (1973)
  - Item 4: Interface, 1971; Publication (Box 449, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1971)
  - Item 5: Interface, 1972; Publication (Box 449, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1972)
  - Item 6: News from Council of AFL-CIO Unions for Professional Employees, 1977; Publication (Box 449, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The American Federation of Musicians, 1968; Publication (Box 449, Folder 4)
    Author: Herman D. Kenin
  - Item 8: Organization and bargaining trends among professional employees, 1968; Publication (Box 449, Folder 4)
    Author: Jack Golodner
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 449, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Setting piece rates: a training manual for union members, 1983; Publication (Box 449, Folder 5)
    Author: Berverly R. Cull; Loretta S. Verplaetse
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The future role of Social Security, 1957; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
    Author: Bert Seidman
  - Item 2: How its done in Sweden, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
    Author: Lisbeth Bamberger
  - Item 3: Statement of Nelson Cruikshank on S. 3350, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
    Author: Nelson Cruikshank
  - Item 4: Statement of Nelson Cruikshank before the Senate Finance Committee in support of adding health benefits through social security to H.R. 125800, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: National Health Insurance Bibliography, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: This doctor business, 1958; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Correspondence - The AFL-CIO Dept. of Social Security has prepared the enclosed leaflet, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Attorneys' fees in workmen's compensation, 1969; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
    Author: AFL- CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Dept. of Social Security
  - Item 9: Reasons for removing the existing limitations on permanent total disability benefits, 1969; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Dept. of Social Security
  - Item 10: Medical Care for the aged, Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Improved protection for you, provided under the Social Security amendments passed by Congress in 1956, 1957; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
    Author: Nelson H. Cruikshank
  - Item 12: Q&A on health security, Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Security in time of need, 1974; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Security in time of need, 1969; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Doctors and the Forand bill, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Catastrophic illness insurance, 1957; Publication (Box 449, Folder 6)
    Author: Raymond Munts
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The vital links, 1964; Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Medical care dollars for better health, 1961; Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Handbook on hospital insurance for the aged through Social Security, 1963; Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
    Notes: Facts and figures on hospital insurance for the aged through Social Security as proposed in President Kennedy's program, incorporated in the Anderson-King bill (S. 880 and H.R. 3920). Revised edition. 2 copies
  - Item 4: Labor and medical care, Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Group health: a better way to good health care, 1964; Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
    Author: Caldwell B. Esselstyn
  - Item 6: The quickening trend towards early retirement, 1965; Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: $50+ Club News - no. 40 (Jan. 1994), Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Union Democracy Review - no. 93, 1993; Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Second National Conference: State Central bodies of the AFL-CIO, 1960; Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Structural organization of the AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Why America needs the King-Anderson Bill, 1963; Publication (Box 449, Folder 7)
    Notes: Flyer. 2 copies
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: What you can do, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: How to organize your union label and service trades council, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Look for the silver lining, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Power of women, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Look for the union label shop card and service button, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Want some free future insurance?, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Weathered storms, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The invisible picket line, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The art of self defense, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Tell the little woman the truth..., Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: TNT in a purse..., Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Lifetime protection plicy..., Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: the Story of a union label purchase, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Look before you leap, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Directory, Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
    Author: Denver Union Label Council
  - Item 16: Directory, 1959; Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
    Author: Washington Union Label and Service Trades Council
  - Item 17: Defense material, 1960; Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
    Author: AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Union Label and Service Trades Dept.
  - Item 18: Labor's guideposts to: Job security, quality goods & service, true prosperity, 1959; Publication (Box 450, Folder 1)
- New York State. AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations).. Union Products & Services, Publication (Box 450, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Official Directory, 1957-1960 (Box 450, Folder 2)
    Author: New York State. AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations). Union Products & Services
  - Item 2: Ralph Story answers $64,000 question here, 1958; Publication (Box 450, Folder 2)
    Notes: news clippings
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations).. Union Label and Service Trades Department, Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: News release - Washington, DC -- The good news that top-quality canned vegetables bearing the Union Label are now available., Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: correspondence - Enclosed is a news release and a Festal canned vegetable label which tell the story of another milestone in history of Union Label accomplishment, 1963; Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: correspondence - In San Francisco, California, September, 1959, the unanimous adoption of Resolution Number 108, 1961; Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: correspondence - During this Yuletide buying season, millions of union-earned dollars will ring cash registers of merchants across our land, 1961; Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Resolution No. 11 -- Union Label Week, 1961; Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Your invitation to go with Syracuse to the 9th Empire State Labor-Management Exhibit, 1963; Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Stop Look Buy - where you see Union Labels, shop cards and service buttons, 1961; Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Women's Auxiliaries News - v.1, no. 5 (May, 1961), Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: What makes 'em tick?, Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: What would we do without them?, Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Have labelwill use!, 1961; Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
    Notes: Pamphlet packet
  - Item 12: This will wake you up!, 1962; Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Honor Roll, Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: correspondence - To All Affiliates of the AFL-CIO National Auxiliaries - Since March 11, 1963, more than 1,200 members of five AFL-CIO unions -- the Bookbinders, Printing Pressmen, machinists, Typographical, and Electrotypers--have waged a difficult strug, Publication (Box 450, Folder 3)